https://www.waffleparty.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Menu HomeAboutRecipes
AllVegan Waffle Recipes
AllGluten-FreeLiegeNeutralSavorySweetYeastedVegan Waffle Baking TipsVegan Topping Recipes
AllSavorySweetTopping Ideas & TipsCookbooks
The Global Vegan Waffle CookbookThe Vegan Waffle Party PrimerGluten-Free Vegan Waffles & ToppingsThe Vegan Chocolate Seduction CookbookOther Authors’ BooksWaffle Parties
What’s a Waffle Party?Vegan Waffle Party SignupParty Host ResourcesParty Ideas & TipsWaffle Party HighlightsGVWP Wall of HostsAnnouncementsVegan Party MusicOther
Veganism FAQsDeep ThoughtsReviews
Waffle Recipe ReviewsTopping Recipe ReviewsVegan Waffle Restaurant ReviewsWaffle-Related Product ReviewsVegan Waffle PhotosWaffle HumorContactSocial
FacebookTwitter
Menu HomeAboutRecipes
AllVegan Waffle Recipes
AllGluten-FreeLiegeNeutralSavorySweetYeastedVegan Waffle Baking TipsVegan Topping Recipes
AllSavorySweetTopping Ideas & TipsCookbooks
The Global Vegan Waffle CookbookThe Vegan Waffle Party PrimerGluten-Free Vegan Waffles & ToppingsThe Vegan Chocolate Seduction CookbookOther Authors’ BooksWaffle Parties
What’s a Waffle Party?Vegan Waffle Party SignupParty Host ResourcesParty Ideas & TipsWaffle Party HighlightsGVWP Wall of HostsAnnouncementsVegan Party MusicOther
Veganism FAQsDeep ThoughtsReviews
Waffle Recipe ReviewsTopping Recipe ReviewsVegan Waffle Restaurant ReviewsWaffle-Related Product ReviewsVegan Waffle PhotosWaffle HumorContactSocial
FacebookTwitter
IntroductionWheitner Authentic Living, the maintainer of this website, values the privacy of your personal data.The following is an overview of our privacy policy, including the types of data that we and our web service providers collect, and reasons for requiring certain information. This privacy policy is subject to change without notice by updating this posting. By using this website, you accept the privacy practices outlined below.We do not sell your data to third parties. Beyond sharing access with our web service providers as noted below, we do not share your data with others unless legally required (e.g., a subpoena or court order).Data Collected & Reported Through Web HostWhen you visit waffleparty.com, our web host, A2Hosting, automatically collects and stores information transmitted by your internet browser. These commonly-collected data include:Browser type, versionOperating systemReferrer URL (previously visited webpage)Host name (address) of the computerDate and time of the server requestWheitner Authentic Living views aggregate reports of visitor data to determine overall patterns of website use.CookiesTo make our website more user-friendly, effective, and secure, cookies (small text files saved on your computer by your browser) are used at several points. Third party services we use such as YouTube, Google Analytics, and Shareaholic, may also create cookies during your visit to our website. In general, any service that provides embedded content, including videos and other media, may collect information about you.If you wish to stop accepting cookies from websites you visit, you can change settings usually found in the Options or Preferences section of your browser. Please refer to your browser’s help documents for more details.CommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.NewsletterWe use MailChimp (the Rocket Science Group, LLC) to store your email address and deliver the newsletter, and adhere to their Terms of Service. To receive our newsletter we need a valid email address as well as information allowing us to check that the owner of that email address actually wishes to receive the newsletter. You reserve the right to unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time, and can do so by using the unsubscribe links in the emails, or by contacting us through davewheitner.com/contact/.Google AnalyticsThis website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how visitors use the site. The tool uses cookies to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Wheitner Authentic Living.ShareaholicWe utilize Shareaholic for some of the social sharing buttons on our site, and sometimes utilize their services for providing advertising or related content. They utilize cookies for tracking user behavior, to provide content most likely to be of interest to you.Advertising-Related Use of InformationWe may partner with other third parties to display advertising, affiliate links, and related content that may be of interest to you. They may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites to provide you with advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.For More InformationIf you need more information about our privacy policy or have other questions or concerns, you can reach us through waffleparty.com/contact. This privacy policy was last updated May 18, 2018.Share this:TwitterFacebookLinkedInEmailWelcome! I’m Dave. I’ve hosted waffle parties since 1998. I enjoy sharing delicious vegan waffle recipes and tips.About WaffleParty.comJoin our newsletter & get yummy recipes.Join>>This site is on A2.A2 Optimized WordPress HostingCheck This Stuff Out!Be a 2020 Waffle Party HostRegistration & info formThis site is on A2.A2 Optimized WordPress HostingCookbooksWaffle CookbookChocolate CookbookNewsletterJoin & get a free ebook with yummy recipes.Citations, Affiliate Links, & Privacy PolicyWe greatly appreciate mentions and links. Please contact us if you wish to post original content from this site elsewhere.Some posts include affiliate product links which help to cover site maintenance costs.Privacy PolicySocialFacebookTwitter
